http://www.objectsharp.com/privacy

HomeAboutServicesCloud SolutionsCustomer StoriesNewCareersEventsPodcastContact UsPrivacy PolicyRectangleCreated with Sketch.BlogUse of Personal InformationWe may gather information about you through our web site in three ways. First, we may collect and store some personally identifiable information (such as your name, telephone number, and e-mail address) that you provide to us through surveys, job applications, contests, or inquiries on this site. Second, we may collect and store information about your visit to this site in collective or aggregated data that does not identify you specifically. Third, we may collect and store information through the use of “cookies.” The term “cookies” refers to lines of text that are transmitted to your web browser when you click on a site, providing a way for a server to recall a previous request or previous registration, or keep track of a transaction as it progresses, so that information does not have to be repeated. We use all of this information to help maintain accurate accounts, to provide and to change services, to provide accurate billing and shipping, to answer your inquiries, to market services and products, and to help make our web site useful to you. We do not market to or collect personal information about children under 13 years of age at this site.Sharing InformationThe information that we obtain from you is generally necessary for us to provide your services and to design new services for your future use. As a general rule, ObjectSharp will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties personal information gathered online about you without your consent. The only exceptions to this rule are: (i) when we work with affiliated businesses, partners, or agents to develop a relationship with you or to perform services for you on our behalf or (ii) as may be required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to you or others. In the case of (i) above, we require the relevant businesses, partners, or agents to adhere to our policies regarding the use and protection of your personal information.Email CommunicationWe may use e-mail to communicate to our customers, respond to visitors’ e-mails, or to inform you about events or new products. We will not send commercial solicitation via e-mail to you if you request that it not be sent.ChoiceYou may choose to “opt out” of (a) any third-party sharing of personal information by ObjectSharp (except pursuant to item of “Sharing Information” above) or email communication as permitted above or (b) ObjectSharp’s use of personal information you feel is incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or authorized by you. If you wish to “opt out”, please contact ObjectSharp with such request via email at privacy@objectsharp.com or via mail at 40 University Avenue, Suite 1301, Toronto, Ontario M5J1T1 Attn: Head of Compliance. ObjectSharp does not intend to collect any “sensitive information”, however in the event that ObjectSharp does collect any “sensitive information”, you will be given an affirmative “opt in” choice for any third-party sharing of such information by ObjectSharp or if it is to be used for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected or authorized by you.AccessIf you wish to obtain a copy of the personal information collected by ObjectSharp or to correct, amend, or delete certain personal information collected by ObjectSharp, please contact ObjectSharp with such request via email atprivacy@objectsharp.comor via mail at 40 University Avenue, Suite 1301, Toronto, Ontario M5J1T1 Attn: Head of Compliance.SecurityObjectSharp exercises generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information provided to or collected by us. In the case of (i) of “Sharing Information” above, we require the relevant businesses, partners, or agents to adhere to our policies regarding the use and protection of your personal information.Modification/EnforcementObjectSharp reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice in ObjectSharp’s sole discretion. Such modifications shall be effective when posted. If you have any inquiries or concerns regarding ObjectSharp’s privacy policy or its compliance with this privacy policy, please contact ObjectSharp via email atprivacy@objectsharp.com, or via mail at 40 University Avenue, Suite 1301, Toronto, Ontario M5J1T1 Attn: General Counsel. If you believe that ObjectSharp has operated in a manner inconsistent with or in violation of this Privacy Policy, please contact ObjectSharp immediately, via mail at 40 University Avenue, Suite 1301, Toronto, Ontario M5J1T1 Attn: Head of Compliance, to remedy the inconsistency or problem.Ready to start your next project?Contact Us
